Andrew Grano

UI Developer & Designer

SUMMARY

Specialized in working at the **intersection** of **design** & **development**.

Experienced in creating web sites & web apps that are accessible, functional & beautiful.

A **problem solver** who enjoys crafting **design systems** and building responsive layouts.

EXPERIENCE

Ycode — Front End Developer

September 2021 - Current / Remote

Developed software enabling users to create advanced websites with no-code. Implemented no-code animations using GSAP, no-code sliders and lightboxes using SwiperJS, and design features using Tailwind CSS.

Netalico (Agency) - Ecommerce Developer

Dec 2020 - September 2021 / Remote

Built and maintained ecommerce sites on the Shopify platform using liquid, javascript, Sass/Scss, HTML5

WeaveUp - Front End Developer & UX Designer

July 2019 - Dec 2020 / Remote

Developed and designed software for uploading, customizing and purchasing textile designs. Used Vue.JS, VueX, Tailwind CSS and Jest.

META+LAB at Cal State Northridge - Mentor & Teacher

May 2018 - July 2019 / Northridge, CA

Mentored & led a team of students in an agile SCRUM environment developing Vue.JS applications.

Taught front-end development bootcamps and classes.

Fluent (Agency) - Front End Developer

Jan 2014 - Nov 2017 / Venice, CA

Built custom responsive e-commerce websites and landing pages for high-profile clients using Sass, Bootstrap and jQuery.

Los Angeles, California andrewgrano@gmail.com (858) 231-6482 andrewgrano.com

QUALIFICATIONS

12+ years in web development and web design; 6 years in ecommerce and 6 years in software development.

Proficiency in HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Vue.js, Tailwind, Git, Responsive Design, UI/UX, style guides, animations, designing and prototyping in Figma.

Mentored, taught, and **led** a team of student engineers.

A collaborative, **communicative**, and passionate team-player.

EDUCATION

Cal State Northridge — B.A. in Multimedia

2008 - 2012

Studied web design, graphic design, programming, animation and video editing.

Learn UI Design - Graduate

2023 - 2024

An online course with a curriculum covering 70+ hours of topics including color theory, typography, branding and Figma.